{
  "caseDetails": {
    "submitterInfo": {
      "firstName": "vijayapandian",
      "lastName": "palani",
      "email": "XYZ@mailslurp.net",
      "userType": "PROVIDER"
    },
    "referralRequestId": "878e0307-a112-49ad-879c-f3a910x95421",
    "referralRequestLineId": null,
    "primDiagUpdatedFlag": "N",
    "referralDetails": {
      "contactInfo": {
        "fax": "(234) 242-3423",
        "firstName": "vijayapandian",
        "lastName": "palani",
        "phoneNumber": "(248) 403-2731",
        "preferredContactMethod": {
          "gdfId": "CM30"
        }
      },
      "referralMethod": {
        "gdfId": "17ba0791499db908433b80f37c5fbc89b870084b"
      },
      "referralSource": {
        "gdfId": "da4b9237bacccdf19c0760cab7aec4a8359010b0"
      }
    },
    "member": {
      "firstName": "NIKI",
      "lastName": "HUDDS",
      "subscriberId": "YKZ3HZN88339830",
      "dob": "1965-01-08",
      "earliestAuthStartDate": "2026-02-01"
    },
    "planDetails": {
      "healthPlan": "Horizon BCBS NJ",
      "carrierGdfId": "d8e4bbea3af2e4861ad5a445aaec573e02f9aca2"
    },
    "attachments": [],
    "caseServiceLine": [
      {
        "referralRequestLineId": null,
        "serviceCategory": "INSTAY",
        "serviceCode": "4282",
        "routingPriority": "Urgent",
        "serviceType": "SNF",
        "hcpcCode": "52",
        "uom": "IS",
        "requestedStartDate": "2026-02-01",
        "requestedEndDate": null,
        "requestedUnits": null,
        "templates": [
          {
            "templateId": "2354",
            "templateType": "Common_Template",
            "questionAndAnswer": [
              {
                "questionSourceSystemId": "25701",
                "questionText": "Request Type",
                "answer": [
                  {
                    "answerSourceSystemId": "ANS1",
                    "answer": "Urgent"
                  }
                ]
              },
              {
                "questionSourceSystemId": "25692",
                "questionText": "Requested Start Date",
                "answer": [
                  {
                    "answerSourceSystemId": "ANS1",
                    "answer": "2024-02-26"
                  }
                ]
              },
              {
                "questionSourceSystemId": "25699",
                "questionText": "Was the service or item for which you are now requesting authorization initiated prior to submitting this request for authorization?",
                "answer": [
                  {
                    "answerSourceSystemId": "ANS3",
                    "answer": "Yes"
                  }
                ]
              },
              {
                "questionSourceSystemId": "31348",
                "questionText": "Was the service or item for which you are requesting authorization completed prior to submitting this request? (I.E. was the member discharged from the post-acute setting)",
                "answer": [
                  {
                    "answerSourceSystemId": "ANS4",
                    "answer": "No"
                  }
                ]
              },
              {
                "questionSourceSystemId": "25702",
                "questionText": "Is there a verbal or written physician's or other qualified licensed practitioner's order for the service you are requesting? (Note: A written order is required prior to billing for services rendered.)",
                "answer": [
                  {
                    "answerSourceSystemId": "ANS3",
                    "answer": "Yes"
                  }
                ]
              },
              {
                "questionSourceSystemId": "31144",
                "questionText": "Was the patient recently discharged from an acute setting?",
                "answer": [
                  {
                    "answerSourceSystemId": "ANS4",
                    "answer": "No"
                  }
                ]
              }
            ]
          },
          {
            "templateId": "99996996",
            "templateType": "Clinical_Template",
            "questionAndAnswer": [
              {
                "questionSourceSystemId": "32139",
                "questionText": "Does the patient have acute hospital needs?",
                "answer": [
                  {
                    "answerSourceSystemId": "ANS3",
                    "answer": "Yes"
                  }
                ]
              },
              {
                "questionSourceSystemId": "32140",
                "questionText": "Does the patient have intense and complex care needs that make skilled nursing facility care safer and more practical than a lower level of care?",
                "answer": [
                  {
                    "answerSourceSystemId": "ANS3",
                    "answer": "Yes"
                  }
                ]
              },
              {
                "questionSourceSystemId": "32141",
                "questionText": "Does the care include multiple components delivered by skilled professionals?",
                "answer": [
                  {
                    "answerSourceSystemId": "ANS3",
                    "answer": "Yes"
                  }
                ]
              },
              {
                "questionSourceSystemId": "32142",
                "questionText": "Is there a plan to provide ALL of the following?",
                "answer": [
                  {
                    "answerSourceSystemId": "ANS3",
                    "answer": "Yes"
                  }
                ]
              },
              {
                "questionSourceSystemId": "32143",
                "questionText": "What type of skilled treatments are needed?",
                "answer": [
                  {
                    "answerSourceSystemId": "ANS25",
                    "answer": "Nursing"
                  },
                  {
                    "answerSourceSystemId": "ANS26",
                    "answer": "Therapy (PT/OT/ST)"
                  }
                ]
              },
              {
                "questionSourceSystemId": "32144",
                "questionText": "What are the nursing interventions being requested? Select all that apply",
                "answer": [
                  {
                    "answerSourceSystemId": "ANS28",
                    "answer": "Insulin Regimen"
                  }
                ]
              },
              {
                "questionSourceSystemId": "32145",
                "questionText": "Select how many hours of nursing per day are required while in the skilled nursing facility?",
                "answer": [
                  {
                    "answerSourceSystemId": "ANS40",
                    "answer": "2 hours per day"
                  }
                ]
              },
              {
                "questionSourceSystemId": "32146",
                "questionText": "What are the therapy interventions being requested? Select all that apply",
                "answer": [
                  {
                    "answerSourceSystemId": "ANS17",
                    "answer": "Supervision of therapeutic exercises"
                  }
                ]
              },
              {
                "questionSourceSystemId": "32147",
                "questionText": "Select how many hours of therapy will be required in the skilled nursing facility:",
                "answer": [
                  {
                    "answerSourceSystemId": "ANS40",
                    "answer": "2 hours per day"
                  }
                ]
              },
              {
                "questionSourceSystemId": "32148",
                "questionText": "Do you have clinical documentation to support this request, including the answers provided to the questions above (e.g. physician orders, history and physical, letter of medical necessity)?",
                "answer": [
                  {
                    "answerSourceSystemId": "ANS46",
                    "answer": "Yes documents are attached"
                  }
                ]
              }
            ]
          }
        ],
        "providers": [
          {
            "address": {
              "line1": "325 HOSPITALITY LANE",
              "line2": "",
              "city": "SAN BERNARDINO",
              "zipCode": "92408",
              "state": "California"
            },
            "copiedFromProviderGdfId": null,
            "faxNumber": "",
            "providerGdfId": "09fbab428da26cae5fdaac632d9512ffa8c61ccc",
            "providerType": "Primary_Physician"
          },
          {
            "address": {
              "line1": "325 HOSPITALITY LANE",
              "line2": "",
              "city": "SAN BERNARDINO",
              "zipCode": "92408",
              "state": "California"
            },
            "copiedFromProviderGdfId": null,
            "faxNumber": "",
            "providerGdfId": "09fbab428da26cae5fdaac632d9512ffa8c61ccc",
            "providerType": "Ordering_Physician"
          },
          {
            "providerType": "Rendering_Provider",
            "providerGdfId": "2b1a27d6eaa3d3129128b3b0875d160931b3d82c"
          }
        ],
        "dischargingFacility": {},
        "diagnosis": [
          {
            "diagnosisCode": "H04011",
            "diagnosisType": "primary",
            "gdfId": "2c949c10ddaf97d4d4bcc329b7903cff2136303a"
          }
        ],
        "attachments": [],
        "caseServiceLineNumber": null
      }
    ],
    "referralType": "referral",
    "diagnosis": [
      {
        "diagnosisCode": "H401234",
        "diagnosisType": "primary",
        "gdfId": "9ceeaa140dcf1eedff95600d2ca6ac0b4c8754eb"
      }
    ]
  }
}
